{
    "subject": "resource/The_Wizard_of_Gore_(2007_film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Crispin_Glover",
    "human_readable": "Crispin Glover stars in The Wizard of Gore (2007 film).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9204238057136536,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Crispin Glover released in 2007?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7582713961601257,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7027317881584167,
            "question": "Has Crispin Glover won any awards for his performance in 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46613556146621704,
            "question": "Are there any other actors who appeared in 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4477367699146271,
            "question": "Is Crispin Glover known for any other roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3934982419013977,
            "question": "Are there any other films by Crispin Glover you are familiar with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35154449939727783,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Wizard of Gore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32680225372314453,
            "question": "What year was 'The Wizard of Gore' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2442912608385086,
            "question": "What genre might 'The Wizard of Gore' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1900923103094101,
            "question": "What is the general reception of 'The Wizard of Gore' among critics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Crispin Glover stars in The Wizard of Gore (2007 film).",
            "html": "dbpedia_6117_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might 'The Wizard of Gore' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6117_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Wizard of Gore' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6117_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'The Wizard of Gore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6117_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6117_53.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention Crispin Glover as an actor who played the role of Montag the Magnificent in The Wizard of Gore (2007 film). Therefore, the information supports the triple that Crispin Glover stars in The Wizard of Gore (2007 film)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Crispin Glover had a role in the 2007 film \"The Wizard of Gore\" as Montag the Magnificent, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}